Guide to the Calhoun College, Yale University, Student Records for the Classes of 1964-2016 Maintained by the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Student records for the Classes of 2003 to 2016, Accession 2018-A-0078
  - Class of 2014
    - Lykken, Adin, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Marquez, Joseph, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Matsumoto, Ran, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - McCarthy, Ryan, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Monteiro, Daniel, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Navarro, Laura, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Nicholson, Sofia, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Oropesa, Cristel, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Oropesa, Susel, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Padhi, Catherine, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Partman, Lucy, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Paulson, Katherine, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Peeples, Miranda, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Peterson, Nicholas, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - Petrie, Samuel Russel, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - Pettit, Marissa, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - Pham, Larissa, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - Price, Lydia, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - Reardon, Daniel Erburu, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - Reisner, Abigail, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 56)
    - Rohrer, Julia, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 57)
    - Rosales, Sarah, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 58)
    - Rosenthal, Chandler, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 59)
    - Sanford, Megan, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 60)
    - Shaw, Christine, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 61)
    - Shen, Daniel, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 62)
    - Shimer, Sofia, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 63)
    - Sikainga, Isis, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 64)
    - Smith, Brandon, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 65)
    - Sobolev, Rachel, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 66)
    - Song, Mingyuan, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 67)
    - Titelbaum, Nicholas, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 68)
    - Tomimoto, Tara Lois, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 69)
    - Tseng, Michelle, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 70)
    - Underwood, James, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 71)
    - Van Cleve, Margaret, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 72)
    - Wadlington, Thomas Scott, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 73)
    - Wang, Dennis, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 74)
    - Wang, Jing (Joanna), 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 75)
    - Watson, Christopher, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 76)
    - Wilson, Benjamin, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 77)
    - Yagoda, Joseph, 2010-2014 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Yang, Ju Young, 2010-2014 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Yorumaz, Yigit, 2010-2014 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Zaragoza, Andrew, 2010-2014 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Class of 2015
    - Abdalla, Basil, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Accurso, Jessica, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Adams, William, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Al Sindi, Muneera, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Ansari, Ahmed, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Arias, Daniel, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Arnold, Monique, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Assefa, Ruth, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Avallone, Cathryn, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Bains, Tiraana, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Baitie, Zahra, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Bett, David Kimeli, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Blaesser, Brandon, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Blazejowskyj, Anna, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Boateng, Kesewaa, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Brink, Laura, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Brunsdale, Elle, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Carr, Dalton, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Cecil, Matthew, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Cheng, Stephanie, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Chiang, Ping-Jung, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Chiquet, Pauline, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Childs-Klein, William, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Coates, Jane, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Cohen, Samson, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Cottani, Camila, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Cruz, Karen, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Cugini, Nicholas Edward, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Cummins, Anastasia, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Deveau, Andrew, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Dudek, Peter, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Dun, Lia, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Edington, Aurora, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Ellis, Zina, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Feiock, Alexander, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Finney, Matthew, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Gardanier, Lauren, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Goldsmith, Benjamin, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Gregoire-Wright, Logan, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Harris, Allen, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Harris, Richard, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Hay, Russell, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - Heung, Stephanie, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Isidro, Ulysses, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Jacobs, Joshua, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Kahoe, F. Cody, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Klopfer, Emily, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Kranjac, Mario, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Kucharczyk, Harry, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - LaTesta, Nicholas, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - Lawrence, David, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - Lazris, Michael, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - Li, Ling, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - Liu, Yuchen, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 58)
    - Long, Austin, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 59)
    - Lynn, Margaret, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 60)
    - Madison, Caleb, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 61)
    - Mahoney, Erin, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 62)
    - Matte, Deirdre, 2011-2015 (Box 23, Folder 63)
    - McDonald, Zachary, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - McDonough, Erin, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - McNiff, John, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Michael, Carter, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Miller, Jessica, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Morley, Thomas, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Nguyen, Cyrus, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - O'Cinneide, Hugh, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Panchevre, Ian Mava, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Pathak, Neil, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Pillsbury, Samantha, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Pincus, Katharine, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Pollak, Alexandra, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Rangi, Sabrina, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Rodriguez, Eric, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Ross, Chase, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Saldinger, Jessica, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Samuel, Sara, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Schreck, Jessie, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Sechrest, Tristan, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Seong, Kyeong-Sik, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Shakespeare, Sean, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Shan, Shiqi, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Shapiro, Noam, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Sheahan, John, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Shoemaker, Stephen, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 25a)
    - Sivaram, Anirudh, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Stopper, Joseph, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Taguchi, Atsushi, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Thomas, Shawnna, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Torkelson, Sara, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Torruella, Maria, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Truong, Hai Yen, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Tyler, Jamila, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Varanasi, Lakshmi, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Wang, Jingran, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Ward, Emily, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Weikum, Damian, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Weissler, Benjamin, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Wiener, Catherine, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Williamson, Kylie, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Wilson, Connor, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Winter, Lea, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Xu, Zi Yin, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Zamfir, Ioana, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Zhan, Peter, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Zhang, Henchu, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Zhang, Yibin, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Zucker, Danielle, 2011-2015 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Class of 2016
    - Adam, Hamaad Haroon, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Albright, Katharine, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Anderson, Amber, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - Annu-Essuman, Kelsey, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - Ault, Aaron, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - Bacauanu, Vlad, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - Baig, Huma, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Bailey, William, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 56)
    - Becker, Samuel, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - Bensel, Kerim, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 58)
    - Beversluis, Lauren, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 59)
    - Bird, Henry, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 60)
    - Blatchford, Georgia, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 61)
    - Botchkareva, Ekaterina, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 62)
    - Bradley, Christina, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 63)
    - Brandell, Deanna, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 64)
    - Bryniarski, Austin, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 65)
    - Burston, Laura, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 66)
    - Campbell, Ryan, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 67)
    - Cartwright, Luke, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 68)
    - Chang, Jonathan, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 69)
    - Coles, Dominic, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 70)
    - Colford, Catherine, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 71)
    - Covo, Mariel, 2012-2016 (Box 24, Folder 72)
    - de Brosses, Cordelia, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - DiLeo, Monica, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Dolowich, Jill, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Dubovoy, Alexander, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Farrell, Amanda, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Feinzig, Joshua, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Feng, Ashley, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Frankel, Alexandria, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Gangwar, Shantanu, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Gau, Jeffrey, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Gonzales, Hannah Francesca, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Gregory, Michael, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Griffin, Anna, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Grinker, Olivia, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Gritz, Derek, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Ha, Joshua, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Haddad, Jamie, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Hays, Emily, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Hemmady, Shona, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Hendren, Margaret, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Hernandez, Jessica, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Ho, Amy, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Holcomb, Amelia, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Humble, Ryan, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Inyangete, Eno, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Jiang, Nancy Nan Xi, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Kaemmer, Graham, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Kang, Steven, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Kaya, Didem, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Kiely, Bridget, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Lanham, Christopher, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Leal, Andrea, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Leao, Jessica, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Lee, Ji Won, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Lei, Vivian, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Leinbach, Annelisa, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Levi, Sarah, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Lewis, Avery, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Liu, Bolun, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Meghir, Alexi, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Miller, Braden, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Minoli, David, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Mohring, Zachary, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Morales, Anthony, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Morello, AnnaElise, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Moreno, Andrea, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Payson, Maxwell, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Perkins, Megan, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Phillips, Rachel, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Pierre, Brian, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Plyam, Zachary, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Rhally, Christian, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Rivera, Caroline, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Rodriguez, Adriana, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Rose, Emily, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Sassoon, Hannah, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Sockwell, Flannery, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - Stautz, Andrew, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - Svenning, Martin, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - Tee, Ren Ling Alicia, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 60)
    - Tharp, Erik, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 61)
    - Tokman, Anthony, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 62)
    - Tolentino, Martin, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 63)
    - Torano, Andrew, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 64)
    - Valle, Evelyn, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 65)
    - Vanderbloemen, Lily, 2012-2016 (Box 25, Folder 66)
    - van Leer, Jacob, 2012-2016 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - VanValkenburg, Adam, 2012-2016 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Wang, Kaixi, 2012-2016 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Warner, Aquiel, 2012-2016 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Wattana, Melissa, 2012-2016 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Wen, John, 2012-2016 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Wester, Jennifer, 2012-2016 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Wilczynski, Patrick, 2012-2016 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Wolf-Sorokin, Jacob, 2012-2016 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Woodson, Donald, 2012-2016 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Wu, Frank, 2012-2016 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Wu, Mike, 2012-2016 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Yabroff, Thomas, 2012-2016 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Zheng, Karen, 2012-2016 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Zhong, Qiaonan, 2012-2016 (Box 26, Folder 15)